[
  {"id": 1, "problem": "23+45=", "answer": 68, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 2, "problem": "76+28=", "answer": 104, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 3, "problem": "59+32=", "answer": 91, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 4, "problem": "87+46=", "answer": 133, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 5, "problem": "68+29=", "answer": 97, "type": "两位数加法"},
  {"id": 6, "problem": "68-23=", "answer": 45, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 7, "problem": "76-45=", "answer": 31, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 8, "problem": "59-32=", "answer": 27, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 9, "problem": "87-46=", "answer": 41, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 10, "problem": "68-29=", "answer": 39, "type": "两位数减法"},
  {"id": 11, "problem": "600-100=", "answer": 500, "type": "整百数运算"},
  {"id": 12, "problem": "400+300=", "answer": 700, "type": "整百数运算"},
  {"id": 13, "problem": "237+125=", "answer": 362, "type": "三位数加法"},
  {"id": 14, "problem": "346+24=", "answer": 370, "type": "三位数加法"},
  {"id": 15, "problem": "720-20=", "answer": 700, "type": "三位数减法"},
  {"id": 16, "problem": "457-45=", "answer": 412, "type": "三位数减法"},
  {"id": 17, "problem": "573+5=", "answer": 578, "type": "三位数加法"},
  {"id": 18, "problem": "637+29=", "answer": 666, "type": "三位数加法"},
  {"id": 19, "problem": "329+30=", "answer": 359, "type": "三位数加法"},
  {"id": 20, "problem": "233+78=", "answer": 311, "type": "三位数加法"},
  {"id": 21, "problem": "149+563=", "answer": 712, "type": "三位数加法"},
  {"id": 22, "problem": "830+200=", "answer": 1030, "type": "三位数加法"},
  {"id": 23, "problem": "314-2=", "answer": 312, "type": "三位数减法"},
  {"id": 24, "problem": "421-7=", "answer": 414, "type": "三位数减法"},
  {"id": 25, "problem": "782-58=", "answer": 724, "type": "三位数减法"},
  {"id": 26, "problem": "654-56=", "answer": 598, "type": "三位数减法"},
  {"id": 27, "problem": "876-179=", "answer": 697, "type": "三位数减法"},
  {"id": 28, "problem": "935-388=", "answer": 547, "type": "三位数减法"},
  {"id": 29, "problem": "437-30=", "answer": 407, "type": "三位数减法"},
  {"id": 30, "problem": "342-49=", "answer": 293, "type": "三位数减法"},
  {"id": 31, "problem": "196+210+385=", "answer": 791, "type": "多数加法"},
  {"id": 32, "problem": "382+199+234=", "answer": 815, "type": "多数加法"},
  {"id": 33, "problem": "222+95+104=", "answer": 421, "type": "多数加法"},
  {"id": 34, "problem": "492+47+198=", "answer": 737, "type": "多数加法"},
  {"id": 35, "problem": "850-256-280=", "answer": 314, "type": "多数减法"},
  {"id": 36, "problem": "928-472-123=", "answer": 333, "type": "多数减法"},
  {"id": 37, "problem": "800+185-746=", "answer": 239, "type": "混合运算"},
  {"id": 38, "problem": "781+132-598=", "answer": 315, "type": "混合运算"},
  {"id": 39, "problem": "278-199+680=", "answer": 759, "type": "混合运算"},
  {"id": 40, "problem": "372-135+420=", "answer": 657, "type": "混合运算"}
]